Guide to the Virtual Library of Virginia records, 1994-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 5: Miscellaneous Documents, November 1994-January 2003; (0.5 box)
  - Allied Health and Nursing Collaborative Collection Project, January-March 1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Documents from the Allied Health and Nursing Collaborative Collection Project including email correspondence and travel reimbursement information.
  - Publications, February 1996-January 2003 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Publications from and about VIVA. Material includes VIVA bookmarks, VIVA informational pamphlets, a VIVA tenth anniversary booklet and a newspaper article from "The Chronicle of Higher Education".
  - 1998-2000 Biennial Budget Proposal, September 1997-March 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Documents about the State Council of Higher Education in Virginia Library Advisory Committee 1998-2000 Biennial Budget Proposal. Material includes four copies of the proposal itself and VIVA announcements.
  - Website, December 1995-July 1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Documents and correspondence about the VIVA website. Material includes resource registry information, VIVA logo design, meeting notes, style guidelines for the VIVA website, general VIVA information, a map of VIVA institutions, Britannica Online information, information about available electronic journals, contacts directory and lists of participating institutions.
  - Vendor and Client Reviews, November 1994-April 1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Reviews of vendors and clients for VIVA. Material includes two client reviews, VIVA participation institution organizational charts, a draft of Massachusetts Public Higher Education Libraries Information Technology Recommendations and a program of the November 1994 Vendor Fair.
  - Authentication, November 1995-April 1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Documents and correspondence about authentication, security, and access management issues for VIVA users. Material includes, guidelines for accessing library resources off-campus, network and security information, a list of VIVA member IP addresses, meeting notes, Infotrac information and two documents about user authentication and authorization issues.
  - Miscellaneous Documents, February 1997-April 1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Miscellaneous, unsorted documents from VIVA Director Kathy Perry. Material includes a list of drawer contents, a list of VIVA institutional participants, budget information, lending information, "Technologically Delivered Instruction", survey questions and a memo about the VIVA contacts directory.